<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="105">
    <author>TisonK</author>
    <version>1.2.1.0</version>
    <modName>FS25_NPCFavor</modName>
    <title>
        <en>NPC Favor - Living Neighborhood</en>
        <de>NPC Gefallen - Lebendige Nachbarschaft</de>
        <fr>Faveur PNJ - Voisinage Vivant</fr>
        <pl>Przysługa NPC - Żywe Sąsiedztwo</pl>
        <es>Favor NPC - Vecindario Vivo</es>
        <it>Favore NPC - Quartiere Vivente</it>
        <cz>NPC Laskavost - Živé sousedství</cz>
        <br>Favor NPC - Vizinhança Viva</br>
        <uk>Послуга NPC - Живе сусідство</uk>
        <ru>Услуга NPC - Живой район</ru>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>Adds living NPC neighbors who work their fields and ask for favors. Realistic neighborhood simulation.</en>
        <de>Fügt lebendige NPC-Nachbarn hinzu, die ihre Felder bearbeiten und um Gefallen bitten. Realistische Nachbarschaftssimulation.</de>
        <fr>Ajoute des voisins PNJ vivants qui travaillent leurs champs et demandent des faveurs. Simulation de quartier réaliste.</fr>
        <pl>Dodaje żywych sąsiadów NPC, którzy pracują na polach i proszą o przysługi. Realistyczna symulacja sąsiedztwa.</pl>
        <es>Añade vecinos NPC vivos que trabajan sus campos y piden favores. Simulación de vecindario realista.</es>
        <it>Aggiunge vicini NPC viventi che lavorano i loro campi e chiedono favori. Simulazione realistica del quartiere.</it>
        <cz>Přidává živé sousedy NPC, kteří pracují na svých polích a žádají o laskavosti. Realistická simulace sousedství.</cz>
        <br>Adiciona vizinhos NPC vivos que trabalham seus campos e pedem favores. Simulação realista de vizinhança.</br>
        <uk>Додає живих сусідів NPC, які працюють на своїх полях і просять послуг. Реалістична симуляція сусідства.</uk>
        <ru>Добавляет живых соседей NPC, которые работают на своих полях и просят об услугах. Реалистичная симуляция района.</ru>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
    
    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/lang" defaultLanguage="en" />

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <!-- main.lua uses source() to load all other files in the correct order -->
        <sourceFile filename="main.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <actions>
        <action name="NPC_INTERACT" />
    </actions>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="NPC_INTERACT">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_e" />
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
</modDesc>